[
  {
    "question": "18 x 10 =",
    "correct": 180,
    "choices": [
      383,
      -268,
      -337,
      180
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "95 + 11 =",
    "correct": 106,
    "choices": [
      82,
      -86,
      106,
      -108
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "320 ÷ 20 =",
    "correct": 16,
    "choices": [
      -8,
      16,
      14,
      -9
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "32 + 75 =",
    "correct": 107,
    "choices": [
      22,
      4,
      120,
      107
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "75 + 28 =",
    "correct": 103,
    "choices": [
      182,
      161,
      147,
      103
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 17 =",
    "correct": 170,
    "choices": [
      -225,
      -277,
      -260,
      170
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "272 ÷ 16 =",
    "correct": 17,
    "choices": [
      3,
      -8,
      17,
      -19
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 13 =",
    "correct": 221,
    "choices": [
      221,
      -26,
      -107,
      78
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "228 ÷ 19 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      -14,
      17,
      -6,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "228 ÷ 19 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      -18,
      -19,
      8,
      12
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "240 ÷ 20 =",
    "correct": 12,
    "choices": [
      19,
      -17,
      12,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "77 + 31 =",
    "correct": 108,
    "choices": [
      -36,
      -124,
      -25,
      108
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 14 =",
    "correct": 168,
    "choices": [
      -219,
      168,
      -234,
      -242
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "180 ÷ 18 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      6,
      -9,
      10,
      15
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "94 + 26 =",
    "correct": 120,
    "choices": [
      186,
      57,
      178,
      120
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 - 49 =",
    "correct": -34,
    "choices": [
      14,
      73,
      20,
      -34
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "24 - 98 =",
    "correct": -74,
    "choices": [
      13,
      -74,
      -97,
      -40
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "221 ÷ 17 =",
    "correct": 13,
    "choices": [
      8,
      -7,
      6,
      13
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "79 + 33 =",
    "correct": 112,
    "choices": [
      112,
      -129,
      -60,
      -21
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "154 ÷ 14 =",
    "correct": 11,
    "choices": [
      10,
      11,
      -9,
      -20
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "360 ÷ 20 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      16,
      18,
      17,
      -20
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "14 x 18 =",
    "correct": 252,
    "choices": [
      -317,
      -204,
      252,
      53
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "72 + 76 =",
    "correct": 148,
    "choices": [
      -125,
      148,
      188,
      162
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "70 - 38 =",
    "correct": 32,
    "choices": [
      32,
      30,
      -5,
      -61
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 12 =",
    "correct": 144,
    "choices": [
      370,
      144,
      -155,
      201
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 19 =",
    "correct": 190,
    "choices": [
      -225,
      190,
      -295,
      -296
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "33 - 72 =",
    "correct": -39,
    "choices": [
      72,
      85,
      -13,
      -39
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "43 + 94 =",
    "correct": 137,
    "choices": [
      137,
      16,
      187,
      128
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 13 =",
    "correct": 221,
    "choices": [
      10,
      363,
      221,
      132
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "22 + 49 =",
    "correct": 71,
    "choices": [
      -147,
      -29,
      -38,
      71
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "69 + 46 =",
    "correct": 115,
    "choices": [
      115,
      20,
      -90,
      7
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "10 x 11 =",
    "correct": 110,
    "choices": [
      -135,
      110,
      -98,
      -319
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "98 + 64 =",
    "correct": 162,
    "choices": [
      -114,
      -76,
      -197,
      162
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "266 ÷ 14 =",
    "correct": 19,
    "choices": [
      -20,
      19,
      14,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "285 ÷ 15 =",
    "correct": 19,
    "choices": [
      -17,
      17,
      -10,
      19
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 x 13 =",
    "correct": 234,
    "choices": [
      -324,
      234,
      -348,
      194
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "285 ÷ 19 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      -12,
      15,
      -14,
      14
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "11 x 17 =",
    "correct": 187,
    "choices": [
      -251,
      71,
      293,
      187
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "238 ÷ 17 =",
    "correct": 14,
    "choices": [
      14,
      -1,
      10,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "72 - 50 =",
    "correct": 22,
    "choices": [
      94,
      -55,
      46,
      22
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "57 - 81 =",
    "correct": -24,
    "choices": [
      -60,
      -66,
      -24,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "210 ÷ 14 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      2,
      18,
      15,
      0
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "260 ÷ 13 =",
    "correct": 20,
    "choices": [
      20,
      2,
      -6,
      3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "176 ÷ 16 =",
    "correct": 11,
    "choices": [
      9,
      -10,
      8,
      11
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "64 + 43 =",
    "correct": 107,
    "choices": [
      160,
      -5,
      107,
      33
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "143 ÷ 13 =",
    "correct": 11,
    "choices": [
      11,
      -2,
      -9,
      -7
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "216 ÷ 12 =",
    "correct": 18,
    "choices": [
      18,
      -1,
      -4,
      -16
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "224 ÷ 14 =",
    "correct": 16,
    "choices": [
      1,
      9,
      -19,
      16
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 x 16 =",
    "correct": 240,
    "choices": [
      -103,
      -361,
      -81,
      240
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "132 ÷ 12 =",
    "correct": 11,
    "choices": [
      -7,
      -14,
      11,
      -11
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "87 + 23 =",
    "correct": 110,
    "choices": [
      60,
      -18,
      110,
      -157
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "96 + 99 =",
    "correct": 195,
    "choices": [
      -140,
      -169,
      195,
      -38
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "20 x 16 =",
    "correct": 320,
    "choices": [
      320,
      366,
      365,
      -229
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "68 - 71 =",
    "correct": -3,
    "choices": [
      -34,
      -22,
      82,
      -3
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "39 + 72 =",
    "correct": 111,
    "choices": [
      5,
      -129,
      107,
      111
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "17 x 16 =",
    "correct": 272,
    "choices": [
      272,
      -234,
      63,
      336
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "44 + 58 =",
    "correct": 102,
    "choices": [
      54,
      102,
      15,
      -151
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "19 + 17 =",
    "correct": 36,
    "choices": [
      34,
      162,
      36,
      -110
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "44 - 36 =",
    "correct": 8,
    "choices": [
      8,
      41,
      100,
      -42
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "27 + 18 =",
    "correct": 45,
    "choices": [
      41,
      98,
      148,
      45
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "140 ÷ 10 =",
    "correct": 14,
    "choices": [
      -14,
      7,
      11,
      14
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "306 ÷ 18 =",
    "correct": 17,
    "choices": [
      10,
      17,
      7,
      -17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "342 ÷ 18 =",
    "correct": 19,
    "choices": [
      16,
      19,
      8,
      -17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "32 + 15 =",
    "correct": 47,
    "choices": [
      57,
      47,
      -161,
      23
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "77 - 23 =",
    "correct": 54,
    "choices": [
      54,
      -74,
      -76,
      -21
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "15 x 12 =",
    "correct": 180,
    "choices": [
      337,
      180,
      131,
      42
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "73 - 50 =",
    "correct": 23,
    "choices": [
      -1,
      23,
      67,
      -74
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "93 - 31 =",
    "correct": 62,
    "choices": [
      -18,
      -53,
      6,
      62
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "30 - 20 =",
    "correct": 10,
    "choices": [
      25,
      -7,
      10,
      32
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "84 + 84 =",
    "correct": 168,
    "choices": [
      185,
      168,
      -27,
      -56
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "81 - 96 =",
    "correct": -15,
    "choices": [
      -61,
      -93,
      30,
      -15
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "25 - 87 =",
    "correct": -62,
    "choices": [
      -62,
      95,
      83,
      -17
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "18 x 19 =",
    "correct": 342,
    "choices": [
      79,
      342,
      -60,
      -62
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "48 + 88 =",
    "correct": 136,
    "choices": [
      136,
      -139,
      93,
      -111
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "22 + 73 =",
    "correct": 95,
    "choices": [
      95,
      -151,
      -23,
      -161
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "225 ÷ 15 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      -9,
      -3,
      15,
      -4
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "150 ÷ 10 =",
    "correct": 15,
    "choices": [
      15,
      13,
      -7,
      -5
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "12 x 13 =",
    "correct": 156,
    "choices": [
      -183,
      -298,
      156,
      229
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "56 - 20 =",
    "correct": 36,
    "choices": [
      36,
      -34,
      -91,
      -35
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "96 + 74 =",
    "correct": 170,
    "choices": [
      -147,
      84,
      -39,
      170
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "99 + 89 =",
    "correct": 188,
    "choices": [
      188,
      162,
      -176,
      124
    ]
  }
]
